<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on Geïntegreerde proef</title>
    <link>jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Geïntegreerde proef</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 10:56:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of a software tool in the training company: Teamleader.</title>
      <link>/jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/taak/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 10:56:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/taak/review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.getapp.com/customer-management-software/a/teamleader/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external&#34; title=&#34;Review of Teamleader&#34;&gt;review of Teamleader&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Tool website: &lt;a href=&#34;http://public.teamleader.be/nl&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external&#34; title=&#34;Official site of Teamleader&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://public.teamleader.be/nl&#34;&gt;http://public.teamleader.be/nl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teamleader is an online tool that offers CRM (Customer Relationship Management) which also offers invoicing and project planning.&lt;br /&gt;
Teamleader wants to:&lt;br /&gt;
- maintain an optimal relationship between the company using the tool and their hopefully satisfied customers,&lt;br /&gt;
- offer the user the smoothest way from quotation to invoice,&lt;br /&gt;
- show a clear and up-to-date overview of all your projects.&lt;br /&gt;
At my training company the program is currently being used by the general manager, the representative, the website admin, the logistician and the technician. They are currently using the basic package of the tool supplemented with invoicing and project planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think Jeroen De Wit developped the tool because he is currently the CEO of the company.
Teamleader currently has this features: CRM, calendar, invoicing, sales, project planning, tickets, time tracking.&lt;br /&gt;
They use time tracking to keep track of the time it takes to complete an order, they can also see how much time has passed since they had sent the bill to the company, how much time they have left to pay, or, if they are too late, they can see how many days.&lt;br /&gt;
The price for Teamleader starts at 25 euro each month, for this you will be able to use the basic package and have access for 2 users. You need to pay for Teamleader each month, and depending on which features you take you will need to pay more each month. The pricing is €25 for CRM, €50 for invoicing and again €50 for projects and €10 for each additional user.
There are a lot of tools that offer kind of the same thing. But this one is the most complete.
The tool works in the cloud, with the information of your products and customers that you inserted you can easily create mails, letters, quotations and invoices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best thing about the tool is that it is all-in-one and online. However this could also cause a disaster if the server got hacked or if it is down.&lt;br /&gt;
What I like about the tool is the fact that it is easily implemented and quite affordable starting from only 25 euro each month.&lt;br /&gt;
I also like that the tool is localised, this means that they adapt the software to their target market. They keep in mind the suggestions of the users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree with the review to a certain extent, because I do not agree that the tool is easy to use. I’m quite sure if you have a lot of experience with it it will be easy to use, but for starters with less experience it will be a small drawback until they figure out how to use it to the fullest.&lt;br /&gt;
What I do not like about the tool is that you need to pay 10 euro extra for each additional user you want to give access to (separate accounts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would rate the tool a 7 out of 10.&lt;br /&gt;
I recommend the tool to companies that are small to medium sized businesses.&lt;br /&gt;
I would suggest this tool if they are a service-based industry.&lt;br /&gt;
I would also recommend this tool to companies with the following departments/roles: Sales and marketing professionals, invoicing specialists, project managers and helpdesk personnel.&lt;br /&gt;
Teamleader requires at least 25 euro each month for the basic package, if you want more  options and features you need to pay more.&lt;br /&gt;
I recommend this tool because it’s one integrated tool so you’ll win time for what really matters: entrepreneurship.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>