<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>It Autobiography on Geïntegreerde proef</title>
    <link>http://jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/categories/it-autobiography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in It Autobiography on Geïntegreerde proef</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2016, Jeroen Tondeleir; All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 15:01:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/categories/it-autobiography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>IT autobiography</title>
      <link>http://jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/taak/it-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 15:01:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/taak/it-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;it-and-me:fe263c8ece748dfdf9c5032d5d9ee98a&#34;&gt;IT and me?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is Jeroen Tondeleir and I am currently 18 years old, I’m in 6I at the Immaculata Institute.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://jeroen-tondeleir.github.io/images/TondeleirJeroen.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got in touch with IT at school, when we needed to work on computers.&lt;br /&gt;
When I was 6 years old I received my first computer from my parents, it was a pc from Olivetti, and I was very happy with it although I couldn’t do much with it.
I was quite amazed with the things I could do with it, especially the games opened a new world for me because I couldn’t access the internet back then.
The games I could play were Minesweeper, 3D pinball and some card game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the years IT got a new meaning for me, I began to discover that I could do more with a pc than play games. Since I knew that, my knowledge has kept on growing and I have started working with Microsoft’s products and some other programs. I find IT a very interesting and handy, but dangerous subject. I think it’s dangerous because it helps us so much in our daily life that we forget how to do things without it. For example a lot of people use a gps almost daily, if it suddenly doesn’t work anymore people will have a much harder time finding out the way to get to a location because they have worked more with a gps than with maps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this moment IT means a lot to me, because it allows me to work more efficiently and faster, it also helps me to get better grades because my handwriting is almost unreadable.
I normally spend at least 4 hours each day on my computer.
I work on a netbook, it’s very small but easy to take with you.
I’m fascinated with the fact that IT opens a new world: instead of using books and looking information up, that would probably take ages, you can just look it up on the internet, there are a lot of handy tools you can use for free.
There is definitely an evolution if I look back how I evolved because of IT, but it’s too much to sum up right now.
If someone asked me if I was an expert, I would have to answer that negatively.
I say this because I’m definitely not an expert at all, I know more than the people who don’t follow IT at school, but I still have a lot to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year I’m doing two internships at two different companies, the reason for this was because we thought it could help me to make a decision about my future and to learn more about hardware and software.
After a month I realized that software was no good for me, but I happily discovered that I was pretty good when stuff came down to hardware. So I think if I decided to continue or fall back to IT it would probably be in the hardware sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now my vision of the future has changed quite a lot, at the end of the previous year I decided that I currently didn&amp;rsquo;t want to continue in IT.
Currently I have set my eyes on Integrated Security, that topic seems a lot more fun than IT to me. The fact why I chose to do this is probably because IT doesn&amp;rsquo;t interest me that much anymore.
However my current choice does not exclude IT from later in my life, but right now I just don&amp;rsquo;t feel like it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Integrated Security is not like Safety First, but it has more interesting concepts about it.
I would love to learn more about safety prevention and another thing that&amp;rsquo;s very nice is the fact that you can get a job very quickly after you graduate.
All these little things have contributed to my decision..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I think about my aspirations, I just can’t think of any actually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life is quite intertwined with my pc, I am using it too much and not only to work for school, I used it too much to relax myself: like movies, browsing YouTube etc.
IT has become a huge factor in my life because it will probably influence my life, hobbies and job later, it also is one of my biggest interests.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>